Narrator: 1
M: We proceeded cautiously along the narrow rocky path.
Narrator: 2
F: They were enormously proud of her when she got a place at Harvard.
Narrator: 3
M: Obviously, I’m disappointed that I wasn’t chosen for the team.
Narrator: 4
F: Life was harder then because neither of us had a job.
Narrator: 5
M: I asked for the bill, but he’d already paid.
Narrator: 6
F: Apparently, our local supermarket’s closing down.
Narrator: 7
F: It was blowing a gale, so we couldn’t go outside.
Narrator: 8
M: He opened the email eagerly to see if he’d got the job.
Narrator: 9
M: A red flag denotes that it’s extremely dangerous to swim.
Narrator: 10
F: We’re never eating there again – the food was shocking!